There is a man here; you are alleged that you killed a man.
I want you to come out.
Not only one; I see two children of yours who died in the process.
Come out.
Something happened. It's like you people were in the house.
Is it a new house? Are they celebrating in the house?
Which kind of occasion are they doing in a new house?
And something suddenly entered through the window and there was a storm.
Suddenly, almost three people died while they were praying.
Please, come out! Jesus loves you.
After Prophet T.B. Joshua delivered a detailed prophecy of a strange event that took place,
a man boldly marched out towards the prophet.
Let's listen to him.
My name is Ubong Emah Willie.
I'm from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
I bought land many years ago.
I built a house and roofed three rooms out of it.
Then I invited a man of God to come and pray.
Immediately the pastor began to pray, an evil spirit entered the house,
killing my two children. And the pastor also died.
Who are they saying is the cause?
They said that I was the cause.
And they want to kill you?
Yes.
I want to stand here and tell them that those who are responsible for that, they are there.
Not only will this issue be settled but they will be exposed.
Akwa Ibom people - thank God you people know what the Lord of T.B. Joshua can do.
Because they have seen it and not one, not two, not three.
I want to tell you that this man does not know anything.
Lord, thank You, Jesus. It's true.
He knows nothing about this death.
The person that sent that evil spirit is a poor person.
Right from the beginning, you had problems with the land.
Yes, any time I went to church, they would tell me that the land is not good.
I don't really know but my pastor would always pray.
I want to say something.
The pastor that went there to pray for you, he used his two legs to walk there?
Yes.
Was he sick before?
No.
Ha!
Even the two children of mine were not sick either.
Your children were not sick?
They were not sick.
Ok, it's alright.
This is a dangerous mission.
That is evil spirit for you.
If you cannot deliver them, they will deliver you.
When the man could not deliver them, they delivered him.
This man is not a wizard; he's purely nothing.
He is just a human being, just like you people.
After that thing had happened, there was a place they wanted you to go to.
You wanted to follow them but later, you said, "No".
That is why they said that you are the one who killed them.
I don't know what they call the place.
They said that I should come with them to a place but I refused to follow them.
The pastor you invited, that died in your house, what did you ask him to come and do for you?
I asked him to come and pray for me that I wanted to move into my new house.
Ok. You asked him to follow you to come and pray for you?
Yes.
Because you wanted to move into the house?
Immediately they started praying...
...the evil spirit entered.
What kind of prayer did the pastor offer before the evil spirit entered?
The pastor said that the land was not good,
that there was an evil spirit there and that we should pray to God to ward it off.
I am a witness. I am from his village.
My name is Ikpe Friday, I am from his village.
We thought that he used his children for money rituals.
Ok. All the villagers?
All the villagers thought that he used the children for money rituals.
He did not use them for rituals.
Thank You, Jesus! Thank God!
Let's go.
To God be the glory!
The truth is further revealed as a man from Mr Ubong's village comes out to testify
that the prophecy given is nothing but the truth.
I am a brother to this man. He cannot speak well.
When this thing happened, the local Government Paramount Ruler sent
a committee and investigation committee on this matter.
The thing took us to Bayelsa State where we consulted a witch doctor,
though he did not go with us, I went.
The witch doctor said that the man was not involved,
that the problem came from the land.
By the time we came back to the village in Akwa Ibom State,
nobody believed; instead, they wanted to crucify this man. He ran.
Then at the end, the Paramount Ruler said that the only place he believed
that they would resolve this problem and by the time he said something,
everybody would believe was T.B. Joshua at The SCOAN.
O thank you people of Akwa Ibom. What an honour and what a privilege!
Thank you once again and I want to say to the people of Akwa Ibom,
any time I am praying, I will always remember you in prayer
for the honour and privilege given to me.
I know many things have happened in the past.
But for you to believe God,
that if I say something, it is from above, thank you very much for that.
So, you have someone praying for you.
So, you have been to many places?
Yes, of course. We went to a place in Bayelsa State.
What did they say?
The witch doctor said that this man was innocent,
though the man himself did not come.
By the time we came back, we told the chief in the village what the witch doctor said.
Nobody believed; instead they wanted to kill this man.
Already, the corpse of the pastor is not yet buried,
although his two kids have been buried.
The community now said that the son of that pastor should be a witness to our trip; he is seated there.
Where is the son?
The son of the pastor is at the back.
Please go and bring him.
Victor!
The son of the pastor is in the church here to witness the whole thing,
before they kill the man.
Victor, please come!
Let us watch the screen.
You have heard it from the man explaining as an eye witness all that happened in the village.
He said that when this matter came up, everyone in the village believed
that this man was responsible for the death of the pastor
and also had used his children for ritual.
They went to many places to investigate the cause of this
and they were told that this man was innocent
but no one believed it in the whole village
and that was how they all came together in the village...
This is the son of the late pastor and this man represents the Local Government.
He's the man the paramount ruler said should come with us,
while I represent the actual community where this thing happened.
Are you the son of the pastor?
Yes.
Okay.
So, we heard what happened to your father. Can you tell us what happened?
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Victor Anthony.
I so much thank God; God changed my life.
Before, I would do something like a mad person.
If I heard any problem, I would run there.
When I heard that my father was dead, I was annoyed -
I was annoyed with this guy.
When I asked my mum, she told me that this was the person
who came to invite my father to his house.
I asked, "How come he invited my father to his house? To do what?"
She said, "This man went to pick up prophets from different places
and then took my father to his house to pray for his house".
I asked, "What did the man put inside his house that he invited my father to come and pray over?"
God did not give my father the gift of prayer but a pastoral gift.
My father was a pastor.
Didn't I say that it was a dangerous mission.
You know that I said it?
I have never heard from him that his father was not a prayer warrior.
The son is saying that he never knew his father to be a prayer warrior.
Why should they call his father to come and pray?
She said this guy's two children died.
When I heard that, I was shocked.
They told me that my father was in the hospital.
I ran to the hospital to see my father; my father was dead.
I brought my father to the church.
They prayed for my father but there was no solution.
Some people came from other places.
Before then, I used to be hot-tempered.
People told me that we should go and burn the man's house and cause problems in the whole town.
I said, "No, let us do it like this, let us follow peace before anything".
Because I'm not like I used to be, so we tried to make peace.
I met the guy and they arranged to come and dress my father.
I even made a list of what this guy would use to bury my father.
And the list that I made was up to 4 million naira.
Can we just remain silent and hear God's will concerning this matter?
I said this because I asked my elders whether
anything like this had happened before. They said, "No".
Since I was born, I have never seen that kind of thing myself.
When a man of God goes to pray for a person and an evil power enters the house and kills people.
If you see those people and you are told that they were killed by an evil spirit,
you will never believe it; you will think that they were hit by a physical human being like me.
Because it was as if a heated piece of iron was used to beat them.
When such a piece of iron is used on a person, his skin would peel.
The two children of his that were hit by the evil spirit
were battered in the head and their brains spilled out.
If you saw them, you would not say that it was evil power that did this.
You would just say that it was a hired killer that had done it.
This thing happened in a way I do not understand.
That is why I said this guy should come and bury my father.
Even this place I came, people said that I shouldn't come here with him,
that I should just wait until he settled his problem
before he would come back and bury my father and take care of my late father's wife and children.
This is a very serious matter.
You can see the condition that followed.
Please, let us once and for all settle this matter.
One thing you people have to know, evil spirits, when they operate,
you will not see them but those who are in the spirit will see them.
They come out like a human being; they too use guns.
They can use a gun to kill too.
By the time the person dies, you will see the gunshot in the body.
They can use a cutlass but you will not see anybody.
But by the time the person lies down in body, you will see that it was a cutlass they used.
Sometimes, they may not use anything and the person will just die like that.
You will not see any trace of hitting, cutlass, knife but --
My brother, I want to declare to you that this brother is not a wizard.
So, there were some evil spirits that used that occasion to strike.
Now, concerning caring for your family and everything,
I don't want you to attach any condition.
I want to meet you so that we iron everything out.
But what matters is that this man is not the one that killed your father.
He is not an evil spirit; he is not a wizard.
I thank people in Akwa Ibom for bringing this matter here today.
I am very happy with them.
When I leave here today, I am going to pray for the State, Akwa Ibom.
This man is not a wizard.
He is not the one who killed your father. He is innocent.
But I will join you and your family; let's see what we can do.
He will not just fold his hands; he also has to support your family, do something.
But not by condition, since he is not the one who killed.
He must do something but I want to join force to support your family,
pray with your family and help your family financially and spiritually to restore the house.
Thank You, Jesus. God loves me.
How many junior brothers do you have?
I have six.
Please, the words of mouth cannot just settle this matter like that.
I want to relieve this man from the condition, since he is not the one that killed your father.
In order to give him a great relief so that he will be out of this stiff condition,
personally, I am going to give you N500,000.
Thank You, Jesus.
So, if this man gives you N50,000, N100,000, please take it
because he is not the one that killed your father.
He will show love to really show
that he is really sorry for inviting your father for prayer and whatever.
He will feel what you feel.
But giving you N500,000 is a way of telling you
that you should remove that condition - that he must do this, he must do that - remove it.
So please, personally, I want to see your mum, your family and your children.
So, personally, this is my support.
I will give the family N500,000 to start something and put the matter behind them.
Brother, see the work your father went there to do as the work of God.
The nature of death does not matter.
Whether they kill you by plane crash or they crucify you or behead you,
what matters is the righteousness of God.
Two: The age at which we die does not matter.
Whether you are young or old, you are this, you are that, that does not matter.
The righteousness of God is the one that matters.
I want you to respect your father.
He went on a mission to pray and for your father to rest in peace,
please take it in that way - that he went on a mission.
Whether he was a prayer warrior or not, he went on a mission
to pray for somebody and in the process, something happened.
Say, "Glory be to God!"
But what matters, if this man is a wizard, I will tell you.
Now, I will tell you.
But I see nothing. He is not a wizard; he is nobody.
Thank you, Man of God.
That house, without deliverance, if another person enters that place again,
the same thing will happen. I am telling you, the same thing will happen.
Somebody was buried there before you built the house. There is a grave there.
We were told that 50 people would die inside that house.
For your information, the place needs to be sanctified.
If not, another person will die.
I want to pray for the people of Akwa-Ibom, the king there in the community and the council.
Thank you very much for this matter, for the soul and the peace we allow to reign
and also for coming to the root of the matter.
This man is not a wizard.
If he is a wizard, I will just tell you and he will be delivered. Simple.
Even if he is a wizard - I will tell you he is a wizard, I will deliver him.
I will come to the village and say, "Look leave him, he is already delivered".
So, the answer is not to kill the wizard but to deliver them.
But looking at him, I cannot see anything to be delivered, he is not a wizard.
Therefore, he is innocent; he doesn't know anything.
There is a pot in that place. They buried a pot; there is a charm there.
It works with thunder.
SHOCKING: Did This Man Kill His Own Children???
I want to meet the family, hand over my N500,000 and also support the family.
This man, like I have said, is just innocent.
They should pray for him because he's confused, so that he will not run mental.
They are trying him now.
He has been crying throughout the night.
This man? - Yes.
Because I see that he wants to run mental. When he runs mental,
they will now say that he is the one that killed them.
Whereas it is depression - depression wants to kill him.
He is not normal anymore. You will see him, he will be talking alone.
He needs to be delivered.
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
My name is Ubong Emah Willie.
I come from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
The man of God prophesied that there was a man here
whose two children died.
He said that one of the pastors also died.
The man of God also prophesied that I called a man of God to come and pray in my house.
Immediately he started to pray, an evil spirit entered the house
and killed two of my children and the pastor.
There is a man here; you are alleged that you killed a man.
I want you to come out.
Not only one; I see two children of yours who died in the process.
Come out.
Something happened.
It's like, you people were in the house.
Is it a new house? Are they celebrating in the house?
Which kind of occasion are they doing in a new house?
And something suddenly entered through the window, and there was a storm.
Suddenly, almost three people died while they were praying.
Please, come out! Jesus loves you.
So, everything the man of God said is true.
So now, can you confirm to us this prophecy from the man of God.
Why did you say the prophecy of the man of God is true for your life? What happened?
The prophecy of the man of God is very true because the thing happened just like that.
Immediately we entered the house, we started to pray.
An evil spirit entered the house.
All of us fell down; then two children of mine died.
Then the pastor died also.
The other people sustained injuries, even I also had an injury.
Something beat us but we couldn't see it physically.
So, the prophecy of the man of God is very, very true.
Since after that incident happened,
can you tell us what happened to you in the village, in the community?
I was accused of killing my two children and the pastor.
So, they wanted to kill me but I escaped.
Later, the head of the village advised me to come back.
Later, the head of the clan told me to get N100,000
and travel to Lagos - four of us - to meet the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Ok. So, you mean this was the problem that brought you to The SCOAN, all the way from Akwa Ibom State?
Yes.
Ok. Now we want to listen to the people standing beside you. Who are these people?
They are my brothers who the villagers assigned to accompany me to Lagos.
Ok. Let us listen to the men who are with you.
Can you please tell us your name and where you come from.
My name is Imoh Akpan Phenson.
I am from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
When this ugly incident happened, the whole community was in chaos.
The clan head then set an investigation committee to investigate
what had happened; that he had never seen this kind of thing before.
Actually, we have consulted a witch doctor at Bonni Local Government area of Rivers State.
We have consulted so many prophets and pastors.
All the revelations have always been that there is a problem in the land
on which this man built the house.
So, nobody believed this; the community never believed.
At the end, the clan head, having set up a committee, asked the man in question
Mr Ubong Emma Willie, the owner of the house, to find at least N100,000
so that we could take a trip to The SCOAN and see the man of God
and that whatever the man of God said about this, everybody would believe it.
This thing happened in a town hall meeting, a community hall,
that was where the decision was taken.
You mean all the reports given were not believed by the members of the community?
Yes. Nobody in the community believed that this man was innocent.
But by the time we arrived at The SCOAN, it was a very surprising thing
to see the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, prophesying that there is a man
from Akwa Ibom State who is being accused of killing his two children
and a man, totalling three people, that the man should come out.
My brother, Mr Ubong, came out and the man of God even prophesied
that we have been to so many places including a native doctor's.
So, it was a surprising thing to me.
That's why I have to believe all that the man of God has said.
He has said that there is a poor man in the community.
The owners of the land have buried a pot in the ground.
That the pot is bringing all these upheavals in the house.
That if the house is not sanctified before living in it,
more people will still die.
That was the prophecy of the man of God.
Even as we are here, the clan head has even called us
that he had been watching us live; that the whole community too was watching.
We have been receiving phone calls since the prophecy of the man of God.
They have received thousands of phone calls from members of the community
and even from the clan head himself, who initiated this movement to The SCOAN,
that they have heard the voice of God
and indeed they believe that what the man of God said was nothing but the truth.
Can you tell us who the man next to you is?
The man next to me is the son of the late pastor, who is brought by the community as a witness
so that he will also believe what the man of God will say.
Right now let us listen to our gentleman here.
Can you please introduce yourself to us.
My name is Victor Anthony Kiddy.
I am the son of the late pastor.
I came here on a visit to hear what the man of God will say about this man who fell a victim.
I came here to know how this guy killed my father.
But the man of God let me know that this man is innocent.
As for me, I love God, so what the man of God told me, I believe it.
Because God cannot tell lies.
Now the man of God told me to leave the accused man alone
and he promised to give me N500,000 and also to take care of my family.
So now I believe what the man of God said that this man is innocent.
I believe because God cannot tell lies.
I am Uyoata Ndeayo Uttah.
I am a representative of the clan.
With absolute humility and respect to God Almighty and Prophet T.B. Joshua
for what I have seen today.
Brethren, the story you have heard and the revelation you have seen today are wonderful.
I want to believe since we have witnessed that wonderful revelation,
we will still go back home and tell people.
I think so many people will believe.
I also want to thank the clan head, whom through his rulership, has sent us to this place.
He has really informed us that when we come to this place,
the truth about this matter will be revealed.
So I want to thank God and thank the man of God for having that privilege
and that opportunity to listen to us.
Today, we have seen the truth and the truth has been told.
To God be the glory! We thank God for everything.
Let us hear from this man. Tell us your name.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ikpe Friday.
I am from Akwa Ibom (Nigeria).
I was down there, when I heard this prophecy.
The man of God said there is a man that built a house, they went to pray in the house --
So you mean you were in the church when the man of God prophecied to this young man?
Tell us what happened after that.
Immediately when I heard it, I ran out because it concerns me.
We thought this guy used his children for rituals, for money making.
I am from that community, I witnessed everything that happened.
Evil spirits entered the house and killed two of his children on the spot.
So, we were so surprised; we thought he used the children for money rituals.
I personally thank God that we have to got to know the truth;
the truth has come out today so that we now know this man is innocent.
Thank you very much. Indeed, we thank God for this wonderful prophecy
that has come today and the truth that has been revealed.
As the spirit of God has spoken, we also thank God that everyone concerned in this matter
has heeded the voice of God and believed that the man of God has spoken the mind of God
concerning this situation,
and we want to give glory to God Almighty for the peace He has brought in this issue today.
Thank you all also for taking the time to come here to find out the truth.
Thank you very much. God bless you.
As directed by Prophet T.B. Joshua, the following Sunday, Mr Ubong is at The SCOAN
with the late pastor's wife, son and some village representatives
who were present when the evil attack took place.
My name is Ubong Emah Willie.
I come from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
Last week Sunday, I was in The SCOAN.
The man of God prophesied that there was a man here from Akwa Ibom
who built a house and called a pastor to pray in the new house.
Then an evil spirit entered through the window, killed his children and the pastor.
There is a man here; you are alleged that you killed a man.
I want you to come out.
Not only one; I see two children of yours who died in the process.
Come out.
Something happened.
It's like, you people were in the house.
Is it a new house? Are they celebrating in the house?
Which kind of occasion are they doing in a new house?
And something suddenly entered through the window and there was a storm.
Suddenly, almost three people died while they were praying.
Please come out! Jesus loves you.
What the man of God said is true.
I bought land and built a house on it.
Then I called a pastor to come and pray for me because I wanted to move into the new house.
As we began to pray, an evil spirit entered the house and killed two of my children.
We were all beaten but we couldn't see the person who beat us.
There was a flood of water inside the room where we were praying.
Then all of us fell down.
Even my brother fell down and his hand was wounded.
So, we took the pastor to the church, from the church to the hospital,
from the hospital back to the church. Then later, the pastor died.
After the death of the pastor, I was accused of using my children and the pastor for a money ritual.
So, the entire village and the clan said I killed my children and the pastor.
They wanted to kill me.
I ran away from the village.
After I had left, the village head later sent a message to me through my in-law
that anywhere I was, I should come back. Then I came back.
Then the village head told me that the only place where the truth could come out
was through Prophet T.B. Josua at The SCOAN.
So, on Sunday, I entered the church.
Immediately I entered the church, I started praying to God
that God should come and visit me and open my file.
Immediately I started to pray in my heart, Prophet T.B. Joshua, the man of God, prophesied
that there is a man here from Akwa Ibom who bought a land and built a house.
Then this man called a pastor there to exorcise the house.
Then an evil spirit entered, killing two children of his and the pastor.
That person is here and he should come out.
So, I stood up and shouted that it was me.
Then the man of God told me everything,
saying that I was not the one who killed them; that I was innocent.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Victor Anthony Kiddy.
I am the son of the late pastor.
This is my stepmother, the pastor's wife.
What brought me here is to listen to what God has to say about this man who killed my father.
When I came here, God used the man of God to speak to me that the man is innocent.
And I believe because what God told me is not a lie.
I had planned that even if this man is innocent or a victim,
he would give me 4 million naira to bury my father.
But now, God used the man of God to help him to take care of my father's burial.
I so much thank God for what He used the man of God to do for me.
My name is Uyoata Ndeayo Uttah.
I am the representative of the clan where this incident happened,
in Nna Local Government, Akwa Ibom State.
And here standing close to me is the wife of the pastor that died during the incident.
She will speak in our local language; then I will interpret.
Thank you.
Testimony Time
Comfort Anthony Kiddy
She said she is Comfort Anthony Kiddy from Nna Local Government, Akwa Ibom State.
I was there in the house.
My husband told me that he wanted to go and pray.
My close friend.
I waited in my house for two days. My husband never came back.
For three days, I waited and waited but he never came back home.
I never knew he was taken to the hospital.
I went to the hospital and brought him back to the church.
The following Friday, my husband died - the pastor.
Since then, I have not been able to do anything;
rather, I have been weeping and weeping and I have decided to leave everything to God Almighty.
But on Sunday, when I was informed about the happening in my village
and later, that the accused person was innocent,
I could not do anything. I decided to leave everything for God.
My beloved brethren, I thank the man of God because what I initially thought
was that Mr Ubong Emah would bury my husband and take care of my family
and do everything for my family.
But when I was told last Sunday, I realised that this man is innocent.
I thank God and I thank the man of God, in Jesus' name.
Please, what I want to tell my Christian brethren is that Mr Ubong
will take care of my mother's burial which my late husband was supposed to have done.
That is what I want him to do.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
I am Bassey Monday Udoh from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
One day, I was sitting in my shop when I heard a call,
"Brother, come; please, I want to see you immediately.
Wherever you are, I will pay for your transport".
So, I decided to rush down. On my way, I met this relation of mine.
So, I followed him into his house.
When we got to his house, I saw people who came to pray.
All of them are my friends; I know them.
When we were praying, an evil spirit came in and beat us
and gave me a very big wound as a result of which
I cannot raise up my hand up 'til now.
I cannot use my hand to write or do anything.
This is making two months and three weeks.
I use my left hand to eat; I cannot take my bath.
So, what happened to me in that house was that when we were praying,
an evil spirit came in the form of wind.
Then the thing was like tear gas whereby no one could open their eyes.
So, everybody fainted.
We didn't know where we were.
This man said, "Let us go and open the door".
He tried to open the door seven times; the door would not open again until 5pm,
before this guy took us to the church.
What happened to my hand is that they used a hammer to destroy my hand.
Up 'til now, I cannot bend my hand or touch anything.
The same evil spirit has destroyed my hair.
Up 'til now, my hair cannot grow on this spot anymore.
We have listened to their testimony, their confession.
Mummy, we invited you here today to let you know that this man is just innocent.
There is nothing like witchcraft in him.
So, someone is somewhere perpetrating this evil.
So, like I have said, I will support the family.
Don't cry; you just take me as your brother and son.
I will be part of your family.
From now on, you just call me in position of your husband -
whatever you feel your husband was supposed to have done or would do if alive.
So, call me; I will come into the matter.
Just let this man be free and forget about that
since he does not possess evil powers and he is innocent.
So, we should not bother him.
As a Christian, he should be coming to visit you and also see you as part of the family
but nothing should be compelled or forced on him.
So, I'm going to support the family. I know you have many children.
I'm going to support your family with N500,000.
Okay.
Testimony Time
He is the father, he is the husband now.
So, I'm indirectly telling you that I'm going to join you. Okay?
After blessing the family of the deceased with half a million naira,
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for the son and his mother.
Testimony Time
So that you will be able to stand as the head of the home.
He prays for the son to enable him to stand, now as the head of the home.
That is Mr Ubong himself receiving deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Who is this man?
This man is one of the victims.
Is he a pastor?
No, he is not a pastor; he is one of those who participated in the prayer.
Are you a prayer warrior?
I'm not a prayer warrior. This man is my relation.
We are from the same family.
You went there to do what?
We were there together.
To clap hands?
At least, to clap hands.
He said he went there to clap hands.
To eat rice or what?
I went there to pray with those who came to dedicate the house.
You have been doing that in the past?
Yes, when I was in the prayer band in the Apostolic Church.
That time, I was in secondary school.
So, we used to go to people's shops - to dedicate their shops.
After that, we would go back to the church.
Thank God you are here to hear the voice of God.
This man is not responsible for the death of your husband. He is just a victim.
He is not a wizard.
This man should be free.
At the same time, your husband was a pastor.
You should accept that he went for the call of God.
If you don't believe that, it means you don't believe your husband was a pastor.
You should see the death of your husband as a blessing because he was a pastor.
They should put this money in the bank. I will continue to support them.
Make sure the children go to school; and take care of the house.
Testimony Time
We thank Jesus. If this issue was not brought here and this man was killed,
how much can buy the soul and the body?
Because that would have been the penalty.
What we are doing is to send you back to the city and your community.
Help the needy.
There's no amount of money given that is enough for what God is using us to settle.
This is what would have taken life.
But God used us to settle the matter.
How much is N500,000? It is small money but for us to settle the matter, glory be to God.
There is no case anymore.
Glory be to God.
Testimony Time
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Ubong Emah Willie.
I come from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
My heart is full of joy because I didn't expect that when I come here,
the man of God would prophesy that I am innocent.
So, I am very, very happy for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Then on Wednesday, the man of God called us and gave us N45,000 for transport home
to bring the late pastor's wife.
So, I am happy; I am very, very happy.
I thank my God and Prophet T.B. Joshua for delivering me.
My name is Victor Anthony Kiddy.
I so much thank God for what He has done for me.
He used the man of God to speak well to me.
He said that the man I wanted to hang is innocent.
I believe what God said to me.
I cannot deny it. I will believe what God said.
He gave me N500,000 to go and do my father's burial.
I so much thank God.
He also told me that he's going to take care of my family and my father's wife.
I'm so happy.
The man of God gave me money to go and do the burial
and take care of my brothers and my father's wife.
I am Uyoata Ndeayo Uttah from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
I am a representative of the clan.
Beloved Christian brethren, I thank God with absolute humility and honour to God Almighty
and the Prophet of God, the communicator, the mediator, the prophet in God's vineyard.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for the wonderful prophecy he has given in this case.
Beloved brethren, we came here last Sunday and we saw what happened.
When we went back to the village, everybody was convinced.
Now it is clear that the truth has been spoken.
It has cleared everybody's mind in our local government and the clan.
When we went back to the village the other time, it was celebration galore.
Everybody was happy about the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
So, I thank God for that in the name of Jesus Christ.
They accepted in good faith that what the man of God prophesied was correct and the truth.
That Mr Ubong is innocent.
So you are here in the service today
and you witnessed what the anointed man of God did for the family of the late pastor.
What do you have to say about that?
Yes, I am very, very glad about what I have seen today -
the presentation of N500,000 to the family of the deceased, the pastor.
I thank God because it is not easy.
Even politicians cannot do this.
I know what is happening in the world now.
I thank God because it takes a lot of time and sweat for somebody to give such a gift.
So, I want to thank God because I have seen that this place is God's vineyard.
So, I thank God for that.
Having witnessed all these things that God Almighty has done,
the reconciliation between the families and also the cash gift,
that was given to the late pastor's family,
what word of advice do you have for people listening to you,
most especially the people back in the village?
What word of advice do you have for them?
Please, my advice to the people listening to me and the entire world is
that when anything happens, you have to look before you leap.
It is very, very important.
It is not easy for you to accuse somebody.
Then at the tail end, you discover that that person is not the perpetrator;
he doesn't have any hand in that case.
So, I thank God for everything.
That when anything happens, you have to look before you leap.
Comfort Anthony Kiddy
She said she is Comfort Anthony Kiddy from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
We want to hear from her what happened today,
what God has done in her family, most especially in her life.
She said she is thankful to God Almighty and Prophet T.B. Joshua for the wonderful prophecy
that was revealed to us, and she is seriously impressed about the gift
of N500,000 to the family and believes that they will make use of the N500,000 judiciously.
My name is Bassey Monday Udoh.
I am from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
What happened to me is something incurable because the thing happened unexpectedly.
I sustained a very serious injury, which I took to many places -
almost three herbalists - they could not heal my hand.
I spent a lot of money but they still could not heal my hand.
But I'm very happy today because the man of God prayed for me and healed me.
I'm normal now; I can do anything.
I also thank the man of God for the good thing he has done to help my friend
to take care of the incident.
The man of God has done a lot.
Giving them N500,000 is not an easy thing.
God bless that man continuously, in Jesus' name.
So, as the man of God said during the service that they should place you at the prayer line,
that he will pray for you, he actually prayed for you
and all this severe pain and problems are gone now.
Yes, all those things went out from me.
I feel very fine now.
We give thanks to God Almighty for what He has done.
Let us hear from the son of the pastor again.
This is the N500,000 that the man of God gave me.
I thank him so much, in Jesus' name.
Testimony Time
PRAYER TIME
Rise up!
RV: Mel Flowers 21/03/2019